const questions = [
  {
    "question": "0 X 1", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 2", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 3", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 4", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 5", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 5", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 6", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 7", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 8", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 9", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 10", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 11", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0 X 12", 
    "answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 1", 
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 2", 
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 3", 
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 4", 
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 5", 
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 6", 
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 7", 
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 8", 
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 9", 
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 10", 
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 11", 
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 X 12", 
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 1", 
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 2", 
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 3", 
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 4", 
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 5", 
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 6", 
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 7", 
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 8", 
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 9", 
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 10", 
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 11", 
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 X 12", 
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 1", 
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 2", 
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 3", 
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 4", 
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 5", 
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 6", 
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 7", 
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 8", 
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 9", 
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 10", 
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 11", 
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 X 12", 
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 1", 
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 2", 
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 3", 
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 4", 
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 5", 
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 6", 
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 7", 
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 8", 
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 9", 
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 10", 
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 11", 
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "question": "4 X 12", 
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 1", 
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 2", 
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 3", 
    "answer": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 4", 
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 5", 
    "answer": "25"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 6", 
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 7", 
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 8", 
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 9", 
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 10", 
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 11", 
    "answer": "55"
  },
  {
    "question": "5 X 12", 
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 1", 
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 2", 
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 3", 
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 4", 
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 5", 
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 6", 
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 7", 
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 8", 
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 9", 
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 10", 
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 11", 
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 X 12", 
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 1", 
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 2", 
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 3", 
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 4", 
    "answer": "28"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 5", 
    "answer": "35"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 6", 
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 7", 
    "answer": "49"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 8", 
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 9", 
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 10", 
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 11", 
    "answer": "77"
  },
  {
    "question": "7 X 12", 
    "answer": "84"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 1", 
    "answer": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 2", 
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 3", 
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 4", 
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 5", 
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 6", 
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 7", 
    "answer": "56"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 8", 
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 9", 
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 10", 
    "answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 11", 
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 X 12", 
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 1", 
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 2", 
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 3", 
    "answer": "27"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 4", 
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 5", 
    "answer": "45"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 6", 
    "answer": "54"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 7", 
    "answer": "63"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 8", 
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 9", 
    "answer": "81"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 10", 
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 11", 
    "answer": "99"
  },
  {
    "question": "9 X 12", 
    "answer": "108"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 1", 
    "answer": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 2", 
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 3", 
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 4", 
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 5", 
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 6", 
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 7", 
    "answer": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 8", 
    "answer": "80"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 9", 
    "answer": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 10", 
    "answer": "100"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 11", 
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 X 12", 
    "answer": "120"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 1", 
    "answer": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 2", 
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 3", 
    "answer": "33"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 4", 
    "answer": "44"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 5", 
    "answer": "55"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 6", 
    "answer": "66"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 7", 
    "answer": "77"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 8", 
    "answer": "88"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 9", 
    "answer": "99"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 10", 
    "answer": "110"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 11", 
    "answer": "121"
  },
  {
    "question": "11 X 12", 
    "answer": "132"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 1", 
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 2", 
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 3", 
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 4", 
    "answer": "48"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 5", 
    "answer": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 6", 
    "answer": "72"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 7", 
    "answer": "84"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 8", 
    "answer": "96"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 9", 
    "answer": "108"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 10", 
    "answer": "120"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 11", 
    "answer": "132"
  },
  {
    "question": "12 X 12", 
    "answer": "144"
  },
]



